Finding Aid for Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti Urban Area Transportation Study Committee Publications
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti Urban Area Transportation Study Committee Publications 1965-1982
Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti Urban Area Transportation Study Committee
0.2 linear ft.
94162 Cb 2
Annual reports and serial publications the Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti Urban Area Transportation Study Committee on issues related to planning transportation systems in the Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti and Huron River corridor area.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti Urban Area Transportation Study Committee publications were acquired through a number of sources.
The record group is open without restriction.
Annual reports and serial publications the Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti Urban Area Transportation Study Committee on issues related to planning transportation systems in the Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti and Huron River corridor area.
Subjects:
Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti Urban Area Transportation Study Committee.; Transportation--Michigan--Washtenaw County--Planning.
- Serials
  - Annual Reports
    - 1976/1977 (Box 1)
    - 1980 (Box 1)
- Non-serial publications
  - 1965
    - Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti urban area CCCTPP prospectus (Box 1)
  - 1966
    - Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti urban area transportation study, v. 1 (Box 1)
  - 1970
    - Future travel patterns, --17 study (Box 1)
  - 1974
    - Final alternative street systems (Box 1)
      (Work paper, no. 2)
    - Final alternative transit concepts (Box 1)
      (Work paper, no. 3)
  - 1975
    - A Transportation plan for the Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti urbanized area: summary report (Box 1)
  - 1976
    - A Transportation plan for the Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti urbanized area (Box 1)
  - 1977
    - Bikeway staging program: location & design of priority bikeways: draft and summary report (Box 1)
    - Unified work program, FY 1978 preliminary draft (Box 1)
    - Unified work program, FY 1978 (Box 1)
  - 1978
    - Huron Valley corridor study implementation plan: draft (Box 1)
  - 1980
    - Transportation profile, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Washtenaw County transit needs study: survey results (Box 1)
      (Working paper, no. 6)
  - 1982
    - Transportation profile, 1981 (Box 1)
  - 1983-1985
    - Transportation profile, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
    - Huron River Drive Abandonment Study: draft (Box 1)
    - (Box 1)